

# ANDREW SIBIRIAKOV

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

### **ABOUT ME**

One year ago I got carried programming. I started by building static sites and loved it. I try to reach the high level and bring the maximum benefit in my profession. Programming for me is primarily a favorite hobby, not just a way to make money.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

HTML / CSS, TypeScript, React.js, Material ui, Bootstrap, Greensock(GSAP), REST api, Git, Storybook, Jest,AdobePhotoshop, Figma, GIMP

# WHAT CAN I GIVE

- My time (I will not freelance in parallel)
- Perfectionism (implementation of the TK or adequate execution in the absence of it)
- Always be online
- I am willing to work harder to meet deadlines
- Participation in the life of the team :)

# MY CONTACTS

Tel.: +7 (977) 302-83-67 Sibir\_91@list.ru Russia, Moscow, Salarievskaia street 10c2 **Portfolio: sibiryakov090591.github.io/portfolio** 

Linked In: linked in. com/in/and rey-sibiriak ov-6a 54941b2

Github: github.com/sibiryakov090591

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Support Specialist**

EventPlatform | May 2020 - present

- Preparation of content in graphic editors and filling the platform
- Create video instructions
- Technical support for users during online events.

# HTML-developer/ Content-manager

Freelance | May 2020 - present

- -Making a landing page and individual parts of the site (product cards, forms, navigation menus, some sections, etc.)
- Creation and refinement of dynamics in JavaScript.
- Creation of graphic content
- Design development

. .

# **EDUCATION**

# Moscow Technical University of Communications and Informatics (MTUCI), Moscow, Russia

"Information Systems and Technologies"

- Training from 2019 to June 2023
- Extramural

# IT-incubator, Minsk, Belarus

React.js frontend development course https://it-incubator.by

- Training from December 2020 present
- Online training